<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creu Seilwaith Ymchwil Holocost Cenedlaethol y DU on Deyrnas Unedig</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/cy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creu Seilwaith Ymchwil Holocost Cenedlaethol y DU on Deyrnas Unedig</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>cy</language>
    <copyright>© 2010-{year} EHRI Consortium.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/cy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Am EHRI-UK</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cy/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cy/about/</guid>
      <description>Mae Seilwaith Ymchwil yr Holocost Ewropeaidd (EHRI) yn seilwaith rhyngwladol sy&amp;rsquo;n sicrhau ymchwil, coffâd ac addysg yr Holocost ar lefel draws-genedlaethol. EHRI-UK yw’r nod cenedlaethol sy’n cynrychioli’r Deyrnas Unedig o fewn y consortiwm ymchwil rhyngwladol hwn. Bydd EHRI-UK yn ceisio sicrhau cynaliadwyedd hirdymor ymchwil Holocost o fewn y DU a thu hwnt trwy: representing institutions within the UK (and Crown Dependencies) which contain materials related to Holocaust Studies to create a strong research consortium; connecting resources through a state-of-the-art digital infrastructure; developing innovative digital research tools; offering fellowships and training opportunities for researchers, archivists, and heritage professionals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact EHRI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cy/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cy/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partners</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cy/partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cy/partners/</guid>
      <description>27 Organisations in 17 Countries Worldwide Currently, EHRI (EHRI-3 and EHRI-PP combined) has 27 partners, representing archives, libraries, museums and research institutions. The project also relies on a large network of cooperating partners and many other individuals and organisations in the broad fields of Holocaust studies and digital humanities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cy/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cy/services/</guid>
      <description> Below are some of the innovative services created by EHRI for use by all: </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
